Narrator: 16
A: a bag
Narrator: 33
A: a calendar
Narrator: 26
B: a change purse
Narrator: 10
A: a charger
Narrator: 13
B: a coin
Narrator: 22
B: a credit card
Narrator: 25
A: a dictionary
Narrator: 24
B: earphones
Narrator: 2
A: a file / a binder
Narrator: 4
B: glasses
Narrator: 23
A: headphones
Narrator: 14
B: an ID card
Narrator: 12
A: a key
Narrator: 31
B: a lamp
Narrator: 3
A: a laptop
Narrator: 18
B: a magazine
Narrator: 30
A: a mask
Narrator: 15
B: a newspaper
Narrator: 32
A: a notebook
Narrator: 28
B: a pen
Narrator: 17
A: a pencil
Narrator: 1
B: a phone / a cell phone
Narrator: 9
A: a photo
Narrator: 21
B: a piece of paper
Narrator: 6
A: a planner
Narrator: 20
B: scissors
Narrator: 5
A: sunglasses
Narrator: 27
B: a tablet
Narrator: 29
A: a ticket
Narrator: 8
B: a tissue
Narrator: 11
A: an umbrella
Narrator: 7
B: a wallet
Narrator: 19
A: a watch